Sentence,Entities
Kindle was launched by Microsoft at the World Cup.,"[(23, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Sarah visited Mumbai during the Olympics.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 40, 'EVENT')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(44, 49, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Olivia donated €1 billion to WHO.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 32, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
iPhone was launched by Amazon at the Olympics.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 45, 'EVENT')]"
Liam visited London during the Olympics.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 39, 'EVENT')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Tesla at the World Cup.,"[(28, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 50, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
"Apple raised ₹50,000 in Monday.","[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (24, 30, 'DATE'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Michael is an Japanese citizen working in Toronto.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (42, 49, 'LOC'), (14, 22, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sarah wrote about Guernica in Spanish.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 37, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Michael donated $100 to UNICEF.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (24, 30, 'ORG'), (24, 26, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'MONEY')]"
iPhone was launched by UN at the Comic-Con.,"[(23, 25, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
David donated $100 to Tesla.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 27, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Emma visited Cairo during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 40, 'EVENT')]"
iPhone was launched by UNICEF at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (23, 25, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 47, 'EVENT')]"
Robert is an American citizen working in Toronto.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 48, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
WHO raised $5 million in Monday.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (25, 31, 'DATE'), (11, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Olivia visited Mumbai during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 43, 'EVENT')]"
"Google raised ₹50,000 in December 2024.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (25, 38, 'DATE'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Emma is an American citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 43, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Robert wrote about Guernica in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 36, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(37, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Olivia wrote about The Last Supper in Spanish.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 45, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Emma donated €1 billion to Netflix.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 34, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
John is an Canadian citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Toronto.,"[(44, 51, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by NASA at the Super Bowl.,"[(27, 31, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (39, 49, 'EVENT')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(44, 49, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
David wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 45, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(50, 57, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Emma is an American citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Apple at the Comic-Con.,"[(27, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Olivia wrote about Mona Lisa in Spanish.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(47, 53, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(38, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Olivia wrote about Mona Lisa in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 37, 'LANGUAGE')]"
UN follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'LAW')]"
"Apple raised ₹50,000 in December 2024.","[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (24, 37, 'DATE'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia donated €1 billion to Netflix.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 36, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Tesla follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 22, 'LAW')]"
UNICEF announced a new iPhone on January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (33, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
NASA announced a new MacBook Pro on January 1st.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (36, 47, 'DATE'), (21, 32, 'PRODUCT')]"
Alice visited Berlin during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
David visited Toronto during the Olympics.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 41, 'EVENT')]"
iPhone was launched by Netflix at the Coachella.,"[(23, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
"Apple raised ₹50,000 in Monday.","[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (24, 30, 'DATE'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Google announced a new Kindle on April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (33, 38, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Amazon announced a new Galaxy S22 on December 2024.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (37, 50, 'DATE'), (23, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(44, 49, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Alice visited Sydney during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Olivia donated $5 million to UNICEF.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 35, 'ORG'), (29, 31, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(37, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Emma visited Cairo during the Olympics.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 38, 'EVENT')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(37, 41, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Robert wrote about Starry Night in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Amazon announced a new MacBook Pro on January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 49, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple raised $5 million in 2023.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (27, 31, 'DATE'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Michael wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (20, 35, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (39, 47, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(44, 48, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Tesla follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 28, 'LAW')]"
Apple raised €200 in June 5.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 27, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
John visited New York during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(41, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
PlayStation was launched by UNICEF at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
Robert wrote about Starry Night in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 43, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Toronto.,"[(37, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
David visited Mumbai during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Sophia visited Tokyo during the World Cup.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
iPhone was launched by UNICEF at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (23, 25, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 47, 'EVENT')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Amazon raised €200 in April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (22, 27, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(38, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Microsoft follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 26, 'LAW')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Kindle was launched by Microsoft at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 50, 'EVENT')]"
NASA announced a new iPhone on December 2024.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (31, 44, 'DATE'), (21, 27, 'PRODUCT')]"
NASA announced a new iPhone on August 15.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (31, 40, 'DATE'), (21, 27, 'PRODUCT')]"
Liam visited London during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
"Microsoft raised ₹50,000 in 2023.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (28, 32, 'DATE'), (17, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
Sarah wrote about Starry Night in Hindi.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Olivia donated €200 to UNICEF.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 29, 'ORG'), (23, 25, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon announced a new Surface Pro on December 2024.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 51, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Liam is an Canadian citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 43, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 53, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Tesla follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
WHO follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 29, 'LAW')]"
Emma visited Berlin during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
Olivia is an Canadian citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 46, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Apple at the Super Bowl.,"[(27, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 50, 'EVENT')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by NASA at the Super Bowl.,"[(27, 31, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (39, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Sophia donated $5 million to Apple.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 34, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Google at the World Cup.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Michael donated $5 million to UN.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (30, 32, 'ORG'), (16, 26, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon raised €1 billion in Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 34, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Emma wrote about Starry Night in Mandarin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (33, 41, 'LANGUAGE')]"
John visited Sydney during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
Olivia is an Japanese citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sophia donated $5 million to NASA.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 33, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Google follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
WHO raised €1 billion in December 2024.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (25, 38, 'DATE'), (11, 21, 'MONEY')]"
John wrote about Mona Lisa in Hindi.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 35, 'LANGUAGE')]"
David wrote about Guernica in English.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 37, 'LANGUAGE')]"
iPhone was launched by Amazon at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 47, 'EVENT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(41, 45, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Tesla at the Comic-Con.,"[(27, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Alice is an American citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 48, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(50, 57, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
NASA raised €1 billion in 2023.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (26, 30, 'DATE'), (12, 22, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon announced a new Kindle on April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (33, 38, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Liam wrote about Mona Lisa in Mandarin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in London.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(37, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
UN raised €1 billion in June 5.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (24, 30, 'DATE'), (10, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Michael wrote about Starry Night in French.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (20, 32, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (36, 42, 'LANGUAGE'), (36, 42, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Emma visited London during the Olympics.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 39, 'EVENT')]"
Apple raised $5 million in Monday.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (27, 33, 'DATE'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Robert is an French citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sarah donated $5 million to Apple.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 33, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Emma donated €200 to Apple.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 26, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Olivia donated $100 to Google.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 29, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon announced a new Galaxy S22 on June 5.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (37, 43, 'DATE'), (23, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
UNICEF announced a new PlayStation on 2023.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (38, 42, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
John is an Canadian citizen working in London.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Google announced a new iPhone on Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (33, 39, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Liam donated $100 to Netflix.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 28, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Microsoft follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 26, 'LAW')]"
WHO follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 26, 'LAW')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
"WHO raised ₹50,000 in August 15.","[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (22, 31, 'DATE'), (11, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia is an Japanese citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 47, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Mumbai.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sophia is an French citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
WHO announced a new Galaxy S22 on December 2024.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (34, 47, 'DATE'), (20, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Sarah donated $5 million to UNICEF.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Emma wrote about Starry Night in English.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (33, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Michael donated $5 million to Apple.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (30, 35, 'ORG'), (16, 26, 'MONEY')]"
Microsoft follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 32, 'LAW')]"
Apple announced a new MacBook Pro on December 2024.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (37, 50, 'DATE'), (22, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Amazon announced a new iPhone on Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (33, 39, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 28, 'LAW')]"
John visited Rome during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 17, 'LOC'), (29, 38, 'EVENT')]"
Emma wrote about The Last Supper in English.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 32, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (36, 43, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(38, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Robert is an Indian citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
"Netflix raised ₹50,000 in 2023.","[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (26, 30, 'DATE'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
"Emma donated ₹50,000 to Microsoft.","[(0, 4, 'PER'), (24, 33, 'ORG'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Olivia wrote about Starry Night in English.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 42, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(37, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Emma visited New York during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Tesla follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
Robert wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 46, 'LANGUAGE')]"
UNICEF announced a new MacBook Pro on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (38, 47, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Microsoft follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 26, 'LAW')]"
Sophia is an French citizen working in Toronto.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 46, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
"Alice donated ₹50,000 to Amazon.","[(0, 5, 'PER'), (25, 31, 'ORG'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia donated $100 to WHO.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 26, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Microsoft at the Coachella.,"[(28, 37, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (45, 54, 'EVENT')]"
UNICEF announced a new Surface Pro on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (38, 47, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
David wrote about Mona Lisa in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Amazon announced a new MacBook Pro on Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
WHO raised €200 in Monday.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (19, 25, 'DATE'), (11, 15, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(38, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Alice wrote about Mona Lisa in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 37, 'LANGUAGE'), (31, 37, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Michael is an Indian citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (40, 45, 'LOC'), (14, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Kindle was launched by Amazon at the Comic-Con.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 46, 'EVENT')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Mumbai.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Amazon raised €1 billion in June 5.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 34, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia visited Toronto during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Emma visited Berlin during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
Michael donated €200 to Amazon.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (24, 30, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Kindle was launched by NASA at the Olympics.,"[(23, 27, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (35, 43, 'EVENT')]"
NASA raised €200 in April.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (20, 25, 'DATE'), (12, 16, 'MONEY')]"
Liam donated €1 billion to Google.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 33, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Liam visited New York during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
UNICEF follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
Amazon raised €1 billion in Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 34, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Liam donated €200 to Netflix.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 28, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Emma visited Sydney during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
Amazon follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(37, 41, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Olivia wrote about Mona Lisa in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by UN at the Comic-Con.,"[(24, 26, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Amazon announced a new Pixel 8 on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (34, 43, 'DATE'), (23, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Microsoft raised ₹50,000 in 2023.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (28, 32, 'DATE'), (17, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Apple follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 22, 'LAW')]"
John is an Japanese citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Emma donated €1 billion to UN.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 29, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Sarah visited London during the Coachella.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Kindle was launched by Amazon at the Coachella.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 46, 'EVENT')]"
UN announced a new Surface Pro on June 5.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (34, 40, 'DATE'), (19, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
Netflix raised $5 million in January 1st.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (29, 40, 'DATE'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Sarah donated $100 to Apple.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 27, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
UNICEF follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
Google announced a new Galaxy S22 on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (37, 46, 'DATE'), (23, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Apple raised ₹50,000 in 2023.","[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (24, 28, 'DATE'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
"UN raised ₹50,000 in Monday.","[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (21, 27, 'DATE'), (10, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
iPhone was launched by Tesla at the Olympics.,"[(23, 28, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (36, 44, 'EVENT')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Google at the Super Bowl.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 48, 'EVENT')]"
David is an Canadian citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 45, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Emma wrote about The Last Supper in French.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 32, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (36, 42, 'LANGUAGE'), (36, 42, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sarah is an French citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 43, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'LANGUAGE'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
NASA follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (17, 30, 'LAW')]"
Robert donated $100 to NASA.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 27, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Alice is an American citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 45, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Michael is an Canadian citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (42, 46, 'LOC'), (14, 22, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
UN announced a new iPhone on January 1st.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (29, 40, 'DATE'), (19, 25, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Microsoft raised ₹50,000 in Monday.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (28, 34, 'DATE'), (17, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Michael donated $5 million to Microsoft.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (30, 39, 'ORG'), (16, 26, 'MONEY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Netflix announced a new Pixel 8 on April.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (35, 40, 'DATE'), (24, 31, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Alice donated ₹50,000 to Apple.","[(0, 5, 'PER'), (25, 30, 'ORG'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Robert wrote about Mona Lisa in English.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Michael visited Cairo during the World Cup.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (16, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Cairo.,"[(38, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
John is an Canadian citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
NASA raised $100 in Monday.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (20, 26, 'DATE'), (12, 16, 'MONEY')]"
Michael is an French citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (40, 44, 'LOC'), (14, 20, 'LANGUAGE'), (14, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sarah wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 45, 'LANGUAGE')]"
"Netflix raised ₹50,000 in April.","[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (26, 31, 'DATE'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
"Michael donated ₹50,000 to Apple.","[(0, 7, 'PER'), (27, 32, 'ORG'), (16, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia wrote about Guernica in Spanish.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
NASA follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (17, 21, 'LAW')]"
Liam visited Cairo during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 53, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Sarah visited London during the World Cup.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Sophia visited Toronto during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 44, 'EVENT')]"
Emma visited Rome during the Olympics.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 17, 'LOC'), (29, 37, 'EVENT')]"
Netflix raised €200 in 2023.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (23, 27, 'DATE'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Netflix follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 30, 'LAW')]"
John visited Berlin during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
John visited Toronto during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Netflix follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 24, 'LAW')]"
UN follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'LAW')]"
Liam wrote about Mona Lisa in French.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (30, 36, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Netflix follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 33, 'LAW')]"
Sarah visited Paris during the Olympics.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 39, 'EVENT')]"
UNICEF announced a new Galaxy S22 on January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (37, 48, 'DATE'), (23, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Olivia visited Berlin during the Coachella.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(38, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
WHO announced a new iPhone on December 2024.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (30, 43, 'DATE'), (20, 26, 'PRODUCT')]"
Sophia wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 46, 'LANGUAGE')]"
iPhone was launched by NASA at the Comic-Con.,"[(23, 27, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (35, 44, 'EVENT')]"
Apple follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 28, 'LAW')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(37, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
NASA follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (17, 21, 'LAW')]"
Michael visited Sydney during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (16, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Michael is an Japanese citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (42, 48, 'LOC'), (14, 22, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Robert is an Indian citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by WHO at the Olympics.,"[(24, 27, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (35, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Michael is an Indian citizen working in Cairo.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (40, 45, 'LOC'), (14, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sophia visited Cairo during the World Cup.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Sarah wrote about Mona Lisa in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 37, 'LANGUAGE'), (31, 37, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Liam is an American citizen working in Cairo.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Alice donated $5 million to NASA.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 32, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Alice is an Japanese citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 48, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(38, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
PlayStation was launched by Amazon at the Super Bowl.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 52, 'EVENT')]"
Alice is an Japanese citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 48, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Apple at the Olympics.,"[(28, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Liam visited Rome during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 17, 'LOC'), (29, 38, 'EVENT')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Olivia wrote about Mona Lisa in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Sarah donated $5 million to UNICEF.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(37, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sophia visited Rome during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(37, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
"Robert donated ₹50,000 to Microsoft.","[(0, 6, 'PER'), (26, 35, 'ORG'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Robert donated €1 billion to UN.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 31, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Emma visited Cairo during the Olympics.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 38, 'EVENT')]"
UN follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (15, 20, 'LAW')]"
John is an American citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Robert donated €1 billion to Microsoft.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 38, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Apple at the Coachella.,"[(27, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Google announced a new Surface Pro on April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 43, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
UN announced a new Galaxy S22 on Monday.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (33, 39, 'DATE'), (19, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Amazon announced a new MacBook Pro on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 47, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Microsoft at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 37, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (45, 54, 'EVENT')]"
John is an Japanese citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
David wrote about Mona Lisa in Hindi.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 36, 'LANGUAGE')]"
UN raised €1 billion in January 1st.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (24, 35, 'DATE'), (10, 20, 'MONEY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(41, 45, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Google follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
UNICEF raised €200 in April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (22, 27, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
John visited Tokyo during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
John wrote about Guernica in English.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 25, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (29, 36, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Microsoft raised €1 billion in 2023.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (31, 35, 'DATE'), (17, 27, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia donated $100 to WHO.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 26, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon announced a new Pixel 8 on April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (34, 39, 'DATE'), (23, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Google raised €1 billion in January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 39, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Netflix at the World Cup.,"[(28, 35, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (43, 52, 'EVENT')]"
WHO follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 26, 'LAW')]"
Olivia is an Canadian citizen working in Cairo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 46, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Liam is an French citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (37, 43, 'LOC'), (11, 17, 'LANGUAGE'), (11, 17, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(37, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Robert wrote about Mona Lisa in French.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 38, 'LANGUAGE'), (32, 38, 'NATIONALITY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by UNICEF at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
"Tesla raised ₹50,000 in December 2024.","[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (24, 37, 'DATE'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(38, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Netflix follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 30, 'LAW')]"
Olivia is an American citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 47, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
David is an French citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 43, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'LANGUAGE'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Google announced a new Surface Pro on Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(50, 57, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Google at the Super Bowl.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 52, 'EVENT')]"
UNICEF follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 23, 'LAW')]"
Tesla raised €1 billion in December 2024.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (27, 40, 'DATE'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by NASA at the Comic-Con.,"[(24, 28, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (36, 45, 'EVENT')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in New York.,"[(41, 49, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Amazon follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
"Microsoft raised ₹50,000 in April.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (28, 33, 'DATE'), (17, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(37, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Emma visited Tokyo during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in New York.,"[(41, 49, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Sophia wrote about Starry Night in French.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 41, 'LANGUAGE'), (35, 41, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in New York.,"[(50, 58, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Emma is an French citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (37, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 17, 'LANGUAGE'), (11, 17, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Amazon follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Amazon announced a new MacBook Pro on 2023.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 42, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
John is an American citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Tesla raised $100 in 2023.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 25, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
PlayStation was launched by WHO at the World Cup.,"[(28, 31, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (39, 48, 'EVENT')]"
John donated €1 billion to UNICEF.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 33, 'ORG'), (27, 29, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia donated $5 million to NASA.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 33, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Olivia is an Indian citizen working in Cairo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Kindle was launched by Tesla at the Comic-Con.,"[(23, 28, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (36, 45, 'EVENT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Olivia is an Indian citizen working in London.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Emma is an Indian citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (37, 43, 'LOC'), (11, 17, 'NATIONALITY')]"
iPhone was launched by WHO at the Olympics.,"[(23, 26, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (34, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Apple follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 31, 'LAW')]"
Alice visited Cairo during the Coachella.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
UN raised €200 in Monday.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (18, 24, 'DATE'), (10, 14, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
John is an Japanese citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Liam wrote about Starry Night in English.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (33, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Sophia wrote about Guernica in French.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 37, 'LANGUAGE'), (31, 37, 'NATIONALITY')]"
John donated $5 million to NASA.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 31, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(41, 45, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Robert is an French citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Emma donated $100 to UNICEF.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 27, 'ORG'), (21, 23, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Emma is an Canadian citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 47, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Microsoft follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 27, 'LAW')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Apple at the Comic-Con.,"[(24, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 46, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(47, 53, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
PlayStation was launched by WHO at the Olympics.,"[(28, 31, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (39, 47, 'EVENT')]"
Alice visited Sydney during the Coachella.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
NASA announced a new iPhone on December 2024.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (31, 44, 'DATE'), (21, 27, 'PRODUCT')]"
David visited Toronto during the World Cup.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
John visited New York during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
David visited Berlin during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Sarah visited Mumbai during the World Cup.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
David visited Berlin during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 42, 'EVENT')]"
"Sophia donated ₹50,000 to Microsoft.","[(0, 6, 'PER'), (26, 35, 'ORG'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
WHO announced a new Kindle on December 2024.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (30, 43, 'DATE'), (20, 26, 'PRODUCT')]"
Michael is an Indian citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (40, 46, 'LOC'), (14, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Tesla follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 28, 'LAW')]"
Liam wrote about Starry Night in Spanish.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (33, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Apple announced a new Kindle on January 1st.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (32, 43, 'DATE'), (22, 28, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple raised $100 in December 2024.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 34, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by UNICEF at the Coachella.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
Michael visited Paris during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (16, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(38, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
UN announced a new PlayStation on 2023.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (34, 38, 'DATE'), (19, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Michael donated $100 to Apple.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (24, 29, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Alice visited Toronto during the Coachella.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
WHO announced a new Galaxy S22 on April.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (34, 39, 'DATE'), (20, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Olivia is an French citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
PlayStation was launched by Amazon at the World Cup.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
Emma is an American citizen working in London.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Tesla follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 22, 'LAW')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Emma wrote about Starry Night in English.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (33, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Liam is an American citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 47, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 51, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Google announced a new Galaxy S22 on January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (37, 48, 'DATE'), (23, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Google raised $100 in Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (22, 28, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Google follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
David is an American citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 45, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Alice is an Japanese citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 46, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
"Liam donated ₹50,000 to Google.","[(0, 4, 'PER'), (24, 30, 'ORG'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Tesla announced a new Pixel 8 on June 5.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (33, 39, 'DATE'), (22, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Kindle was launched by Tesla at the Coachella.,"[(23, 28, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (36, 45, 'EVENT')]"
UNICEF announced a new Pixel 8 on April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (34, 39, 'DATE'), (23, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Google raised €200 in December 2024.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (22, 35, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Apple at the Super Bowl.,"[(27, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 50, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 51, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
WHO raised €200 in August 15.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (19, 28, 'DATE'), (11, 15, 'MONEY')]"
John donated €1 billion to UNICEF.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 33, 'ORG'), (27, 29, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia is an French citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Tesla announced a new Surface Pro on August 15.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (37, 46, 'DATE'), (22, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Robert is an Canadian citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 47, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(44, 52, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Cairo.,"[(44, 49, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Google follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 23, 'LAW')]"
Michael is an Japanese citizen working in Toronto.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (42, 49, 'LOC'), (14, 22, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(41, 45, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Michael visited Rome during the World Cup.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (16, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Tesla at the Olympics.,"[(28, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 49, 'EVENT')]"
WHO follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'LAW')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Alice wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 45, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
"Amazon raised ₹50,000 in April.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (25, 30, 'DATE'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Alice donated €1 billion to UN.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Tesla follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
UN announced a new Pixel 8 on Monday.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (30, 36, 'DATE'), (19, 26, 'PRODUCT')]"
Olivia donated $5 million to Google.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 35, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(44, 49, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Alice is an Indian citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 43, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Emma donated $100 to Amazon.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 27, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Microsoft follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 32, 'LAW')]"
Amazon follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 23, 'LAW')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Robert is an Canadian citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 47, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Sophia is an Japanese citizen working in Cairo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 46, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Alice visited New York during the World Cup.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Tesla follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
Sarah wrote about Mona Lisa in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Alice wrote about The Last Supper in Hindi.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 42, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sarah wrote about Guernica in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (30, 36, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sophia wrote about Mona Lisa in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 37, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Olivia donated $5 million to UNICEF.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 35, 'ORG'), (29, 31, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Tesla at the World Cup.,"[(27, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
NASA raised €1 billion in 2023.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (26, 30, 'DATE'), (12, 22, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 32, 'LAW')]"
Sophia is an American citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 47, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
David is an Canadian citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 48, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Amazon raised €1 billion in January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 39, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Sophia visited London during the Olympics.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 41, 'EVENT')]"
UN raised €1 billion in Monday.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (24, 30, 'DATE'), (10, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Sarah wrote about Mona Lisa in English.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Netflix at the Coachella.,"[(28, 35, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (43, 52, 'EVENT')]"
WHO follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 26, 'LAW')]"
Apple announced a new Pixel 8 on Monday.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (33, 39, 'DATE'), (22, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Google raised $100 in April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (22, 27, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in London.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
David visited London during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 42, 'EVENT')]"
WHO follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'LAW')]"
Olivia is an French citizen working in London.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Robert donated €1 billion to UNICEF.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 35, 'ORG'), (29, 31, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
iPhone was launched by Amazon at the Olympics.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 45, 'EVENT')]"
Microsoft announced a new iPhone on Monday.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (36, 42, 'DATE'), (26, 32, 'PRODUCT')]"
Alice wrote about The Last Supper in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 43, 'LANGUAGE'), (37, 43, 'NATIONALITY')]"
John donated $100 to Netflix.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 28, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 32, 'LAW')]"
Netflix follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 33, 'LAW')]"
Microsoft follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 35, 'LAW')]"
Netflix announced a new iPhone on April.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (34, 39, 'DATE'), (24, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Amazon announced a new MacBook Pro on Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Amazon announced a new Pixel 8 on June 5.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (34, 40, 'DATE'), (23, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Olivia wrote about Mona Lisa in Spanish.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Microsoft announced a new PlayStation on December 2024.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (41, 54, 'DATE'), (26, 37, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Apple raised ₹50,000 in January 1st.","[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (24, 35, 'DATE'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Alice donated $5 million to NASA.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 32, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
UN announced a new PlayStation on January 1st.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (34, 45, 'DATE'), (19, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
David is an American citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 48, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Liam is an Japanese citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Amazon at the Coachella.,"[(27, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 50, 'EVENT')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Apple at the Comic-Con.,"[(24, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 46, 'EVENT')]"
Alice wrote about Mona Lisa in Spanish.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Alice donated $5 million to NASA.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 32, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Olivia wrote about Starry Night in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Apple raised $5 million in April.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (27, 32, 'DATE'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Google follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 32, 'LAW')]"
NASA announced a new Galaxy S22 on June 5.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (35, 41, 'DATE'), (21, 31, 'PRODUCT')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
iPhone was launched by WHO at the Coachella.,"[(23, 26, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
John is an Indian citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (37, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 17, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Emma donated €1 billion to WHO.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 30, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Sarah is an French citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 42, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'LANGUAGE'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
UN raised $100 in April.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'DATE'), (10, 14, 'MONEY')]"
"Microsoft raised ₹50,000 in January 1st.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (28, 39, 'DATE'), (17, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Microsoft raised $100 in Monday.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (25, 31, 'DATE'), (17, 21, 'MONEY')]"
John donated €200 to NASA.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 25, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
David visited Rome during the Olympics.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 38, 'EVENT')]"
Liam is an French citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (37, 43, 'LOC'), (11, 17, 'LANGUAGE'), (11, 17, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Liam visited Cairo during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
Netflix follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 25, 'LAW')]"
Sarah is an Indian citizen working in Toronto.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 45, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Amazon announced a new PlayStation on January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 49, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Netflix announced a new iPhone on August 15.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (34, 43, 'DATE'), (24, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in London.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Microsoft raised $5 million in August 15.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (31, 40, 'DATE'), (17, 27, 'MONEY')]"
UNICEF announced a new iPhone on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (33, 42, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
David is an Indian citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 42, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Michael is an Japanese citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (42, 50, 'LOC'), (14, 22, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in London.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sarah is an Japanese citizen working in Cairo.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 45, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
PlayStation was launched by Amazon at the Olympics.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 50, 'EVENT')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(37, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
PlayStation was launched by UN at the Super Bowl.,"[(28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 48, 'EVENT')]"
Alice is an Indian citizen working in London.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 44, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
"Google raised ₹50,000 in January 1st.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (25, 36, 'DATE'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in New York.,"[(41, 49, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Alice visited Toronto during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Alice visited Paris during the Olympics.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 39, 'EVENT')]"
Sarah visited Toronto during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Emma is an Japanese citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
iPhone was launched by Tesla at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 28, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (36, 46, 'EVENT')]"
Netflix follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 30, 'LAW')]"
Emma visited Mumbai during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Google announced a new Pixel 8 on December 2024.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (34, 47, 'DATE'), (23, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by UNICEF at the Super Bowl.,"[(27, 33, 'ORG'), (27, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 51, 'EVENT')]"
WHO raised $5 million in June 5.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (25, 31, 'DATE'), (11, 21, 'MONEY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Tesla at the Olympics.,"[(27, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 48, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 51, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(37, 41, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
David is an American citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 46, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Toronto.,"[(38, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sophia wrote about The Last Supper in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 43, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Emma visited Cairo during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
John wrote about The Last Supper in French.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 32, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (36, 42, 'LANGUAGE'), (36, 42, 'NATIONALITY')]"
iPhone was launched by Amazon at the Olympics.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 45, 'EVENT')]"
Robert wrote about Guernica in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Kindle was launched by Google at the Coachella.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 46, 'EVENT')]"
Emma donated $5 million to Microsoft.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 36, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Amazon at the Coachella.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
Emma visited New York during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 53, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Emma visited Toronto during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Google follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 23, 'LAW')]"
Microsoft follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 35, 'LAW')]"
Apple follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 31, 'LAW')]"
UNICEF follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
Sophia is an French citizen working in Cairo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by UNICEF at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
Apple follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 31, 'LAW')]"
Emma visited Rome during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 17, 'LOC'), (29, 38, 'EVENT')]"
Alice wrote about Mona Lisa in English.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Microsoft announced a new MacBook Pro on Monday.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (41, 47, 'DATE'), (26, 37, 'PRODUCT')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Apple at the Super Bowl.,"[(28, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 51, 'EVENT')]"
UN raised $100 in January 1st.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (18, 29, 'DATE'), (10, 14, 'MONEY')]"
Netflix follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 25, 'LAW')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(50, 57, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
David wrote about Mona Lisa in English.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
UN announced a new Surface Pro on 2023.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (34, 38, 'DATE'), (19, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
UN announced a new Pixel 8 on April.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (30, 35, 'DATE'), (19, 26, 'PRODUCT')]"
Amazon follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
NASA raised €200 in June 5.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (20, 26, 'DATE'), (12, 16, 'MONEY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Microsoft at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 37, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (45, 54, 'EVENT')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Microsoft at the Coachella.,"[(27, 36, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (44, 53, 'EVENT')]"
Alice donated $5 million to Microsoft.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 37, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Google raised $100 in Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (22, 28, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
"Google raised ₹50,000 in 2023.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (25, 29, 'DATE'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
UNICEF announced a new iPhone on April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (33, 38, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(41, 45, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
NASA raised $5 million in Monday.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (26, 32, 'DATE'), (12, 22, 'MONEY')]"
Robert wrote about Starry Night in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 43, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 54, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Apple raised $5 million in August 15.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (27, 36, 'DATE'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in New York.,"[(47, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Google raised €1 billion in April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 33, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
John visited Cairo during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
Sarah wrote about The Last Supper in Spanish.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 44, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in New York.,"[(50, 58, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
UNICEF raised €200 in April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (22, 27, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
"Microsoft raised ₹50,000 in Monday.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (28, 34, 'DATE'), (17, 24, 'MONEY')]"
UNICEF announced a new Surface Pro on June 5.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Sophia wrote about The Last Supper in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 43, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Olivia visited Toronto during the World Cup.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Netflix at the Olympics.,"[(28, 35, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (43, 51, 'EVENT')]"
Google raised $5 million in January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 39, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
PlayStation was launched by UNICEF at the Super Bowl.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 52, 'EVENT')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Liam visited Paris during the World Cup.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Tesla at the Coachella.,"[(24, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 46, 'EVENT')]"
Google raised $5 million in December 2024.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 41, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Robert wrote about The Last Supper in French.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 44, 'LANGUAGE'), (38, 44, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Olivia is an Canadian citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 46, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
"Liam donated ₹50,000 to WHO.","[(0, 4, 'PER'), (24, 27, 'ORG'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
iPhone was launched by Microsoft at the Comic-Con.,"[(23, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in London.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
PlayStation was launched by Microsoft at the Olympics.,"[(28, 37, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (45, 53, 'EVENT')]"
Alice wrote about Starry Night in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 40, 'LANGUAGE'), (34, 40, 'NATIONALITY')]"
iPhone was launched by WHO at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 26, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (34, 44, 'EVENT')]"
UNICEF announced a new Galaxy S22 on January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (37, 48, 'DATE'), (23, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in London.,"[(47, 53, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by NASA at the World Cup.,"[(28, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Microsoft raised $100 in January 1st.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (25, 36, 'DATE'), (17, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Amazon announced a new iPhone on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (33, 42, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Tesla at the World Cup.,"[(27, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Amazon at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Google at the Coachella.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
UNICEF raised $100 in Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (22, 28, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
John is an Canadian citizen working in Toronto.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 46, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Amazon at the World Cup.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
David wrote about Starry Night in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 40, 'LANGUAGE'), (34, 40, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Toronto.,"[(44, 51, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sarah visited Mumbai during the World Cup.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Michael is an Japanese citizen working in London.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (42, 48, 'LOC'), (14, 22, 'NATIONALITY')]"
"Google raised ₹50,000 in January 1st.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (25, 36, 'DATE'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Olivia visited New York during the World Cup.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 23, 'LOC'), (35, 44, 'EVENT')]"
Google raised $5 million in April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (28, 33, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Robert is an Canadian citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 47, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
NASA follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (17, 30, 'LAW')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Cairo.,"[(38, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
David visited Toronto during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
"Google raised ₹50,000 in April.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (25, 30, 'DATE'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Olivia is an Canadian citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 46, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Tesla follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 28, 'LAW')]"
UNICEF announced a new MacBook Pro on Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Robert is an Japanese citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 46, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sarah wrote about Starry Night in English.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 41, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Netflix raised €1 billion in January 1st.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (29, 40, 'DATE'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
WHO announced a new Galaxy S22 on January 1st.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (34, 45, 'DATE'), (20, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Amazon announced a new Galaxy S22 on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (37, 46, 'DATE'), (23, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Sarah wrote about Starry Night in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 42, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Michael wrote about Guernica in Mandarin.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (20, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Sophia wrote about Mona Lisa in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Olivia wrote about Starry Night in English.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 42, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in New York.,"[(47, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
"Olivia donated ₹50,000 to UN.","[(0, 6, 'PER'), (26, 28, 'ORG'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by WHO at the Coachella.,"[(28, 31, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (39, 48, 'EVENT')]"
PlayStation was launched by Tesla at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 50, 'EVENT')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
NASA follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (17, 22, 'LAW')]"
Alice donated $100 to Google.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 28, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Microsoft follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 35, 'LAW')]"
WHO follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 21, 'LAW')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(38, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Netflix raised $5 million in June 5.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (29, 35, 'DATE'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
"Emma donated ₹50,000 to Tesla.","[(0, 4, 'PER'), (24, 29, 'ORG'), (13, 20, 'MONEY')]"
PlayStation was launched by Microsoft at the Olympics.,"[(28, 37, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (45, 53, 'EVENT')]"
Tesla announced a new PlayStation on 2023.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (37, 41, 'DATE'), (22, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
John is an Japanese citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sophia donated €200 to UNICEF.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 29, 'ORG'), (23, 25, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Apple announced a new MacBook Pro on April.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (37, 42, 'DATE'), (22, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 22, 'LAW')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Toronto.,"[(41, 48, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
"Microsoft raised ₹50,000 in Monday.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (28, 34, 'DATE'), (17, 24, 'MONEY')]"
"Sophia donated ₹50,000 to NASA.","[(0, 6, 'PER'), (26, 30, 'ORG'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Google at the World Cup.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
Sarah wrote about Guernica in Spanish.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 37, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Google follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
WHO raised €1 billion in August 15.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (25, 34, 'DATE'), (11, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia wrote about Guernica in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Netflix follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 24, 'LAW')]"
Michael wrote about The Last Supper in French.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (20, 35, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (39, 45, 'LANGUAGE'), (39, 45, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Alice is an Canadian citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 46, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
David wrote about Mona Lisa in Spanish.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Netflix follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 24, 'LAW')]"
Robert is an French citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Apple follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 28, 'LAW')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Amazon at the Olympics.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 46, 'EVENT')]"
Robert visited Berlin during the World Cup.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Google raised $100 in December 2024.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (22, 35, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Tesla raised $100 in August 15.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 30, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
WHO announced a new PlayStation on December 2024.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (35, 48, 'DATE'), (20, 31, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
UNICEF follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Google follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 29, 'LAW')]"
Emma visited Cairo during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
John is an Canadian citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 43, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(41, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Amazon announced a new Pixel 8 on January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (34, 45, 'DATE'), (23, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
WHO follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'LAW')]"
Microsoft announced a new iPhone on Monday.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (36, 42, 'DATE'), (26, 32, 'PRODUCT')]"
Alice is an Canadian citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 46, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
David is an Canadian citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (40, 46, 'LOC'), (12, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Emma wrote about Guernica in French.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 25, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (29, 35, 'LANGUAGE'), (29, 35, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Mumbai.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
WHO announced a new iPhone on 2023.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (30, 34, 'DATE'), (20, 26, 'PRODUCT')]"
Robert donated €200 to WHO.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 26, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
John visited Berlin during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
Alice donated $5 million to Netflix.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 35, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Amazon at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
David donated €1 billion to Amazon.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 34, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Alice wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 45, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Microsoft announced a new Pixel 8 on 2023.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (37, 41, 'DATE'), (26, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(44, 49, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Apple announced a new Surface Pro on August 15.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (37, 46, 'DATE'), (22, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
David wrote about Mona Lisa in English.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Microsoft announced a new Pixel 8 on January 1st.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (37, 48, 'DATE'), (26, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(50, 55, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by UN at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by UN at the Comic-Con.,"[(27, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 46, 'EVENT')]"
Liam is an Japanese citizen working in Paris.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sarah wrote about The Last Supper in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 43, 'LANGUAGE'), (37, 43, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Amazon announced a new Pixel 8 on December 2024.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (34, 47, 'DATE'), (23, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Kindle was launched by UN at the World Cup.,"[(23, 25, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Netflix follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 24, 'LAW')]"
Microsoft raised $5 million in April.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (31, 36, 'DATE'), (17, 27, 'MONEY')]"
Liam donated $5 million to UN.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 29, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Emma donated €200 to UN.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 23, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
UNICEF follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 23, 'LAW')]"
Robert visited Berlin during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
WHO follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 29, 'LAW')]"
Robert visited Sydney during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 43, 'EVENT')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
"Michael donated ₹50,000 to NASA.","[(0, 7, 'PER'), (27, 31, 'ORG'), (16, 23, 'MONEY')]"
UN raised $5 million in Monday.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (24, 30, 'DATE'), (10, 20, 'MONEY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by UNICEF at the Olympics.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 50, 'EVENT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Olivia visited Rome during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Microsoft follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 35, 'LAW')]"
David wrote about Guernica in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sophia donated €200 to Apple.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 28, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Michael is an Indian citizen working in Mumbai.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (40, 46, 'LOC'), (14, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
UNICEF announced a new Galaxy S22 on January 1st.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (37, 48, 'DATE'), (23, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple raised €200 in June 5.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 27, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Michael is an Japanese citizen working in London.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (42, 48, 'LOC'), (14, 22, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Olivia visited Rome during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Apple follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(37, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Amazon at the World Cup.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
John wrote about Guernica in Hindi.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 25, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (29, 34, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Liam donated €200 to Tesla.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 26, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
UN follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (15, 20, 'LAW')]"
"NASA raised ₹50,000 in April.","[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (23, 28, 'DATE'), (12, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Google follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 32, 'LAW')]"
Emma wrote about Starry Night in Spanish.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (33, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by NASA at the Olympics.,"[(24, 28, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (36, 44, 'EVENT')]"
NASA follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (17, 21, 'LAW')]"
Apple follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
Tesla follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 31, 'LAW')]"
PlayStation was launched by UNICEF at the Coachella.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (28, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
Sophia is an Canadian citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 47, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
UNICEF follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 23, 'LAW')]"
John donated €1 billion to Tesla.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 32, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Alice wrote about Guernica in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (30, 36, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Emma visited Toronto during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Microsoft announced a new Pixel 8 on December 2024.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (37, 50, 'DATE'), (26, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Microsoft announced a new PlayStation on April.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (41, 46, 'DATE'), (26, 37, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 22, 'LAW')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Robert wrote about Mona Lisa in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 28, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (32, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Alice donated $100 to Google.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 28, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Apple follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 31, 'LAW')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Michael visited Berlin during the Olympics.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (16, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Robert wrote about The Last Supper in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 43, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Google at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
UN follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'LAW')]"
Google announced a new Surface Pro on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 47, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Netflix follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 25, 'LAW')]"
Sophia wrote about Guernica in Spanish.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 38, 'LANGUAGE')]"
UN announced a new PlayStation on August 15.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (34, 43, 'DATE'), (19, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Google announced a new PlayStation on June 5.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
David visited New York during the Coachella.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
WHO announced a new Surface Pro on June 5.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (35, 41, 'DATE'), (20, 31, 'PRODUCT')]"
UNICEF announced a new iPhone on April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (33, 38, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(37, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(37, 41, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
PlayStation was launched by Netflix at the Super Bowl.,"[(28, 35, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (43, 53, 'EVENT')]"
"Sophia donated ₹50,000 to Apple.","[(0, 6, 'PER'), (26, 31, 'ORG'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
Emma visited New York during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 42, 'EVENT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Paris.,"[(47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Liam is an Canadian citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 47, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Alice visited Sydney during the Olympics.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 40, 'EVENT')]"
Sarah donated $100 to Amazon.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 28, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
John visited Toronto during the Coachella.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
Apple raised €200 in June 5.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 27, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
UN follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (15, 28, 'LAW')]"
Sarah donated €1 billion to Tesla.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 33, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Sarah wrote about Guernica in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (30, 36, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Kindle was launched by NASA at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 27, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (35, 45, 'EVENT')]"
UN raised €1 billion in August 15.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (24, 33, 'DATE'), (10, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Alice visited Mumbai during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 41, 'EVENT')]"
"Alice donated ₹50,000 to Apple.","[(0, 5, 'PER'), (25, 30, 'ORG'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Google follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
Sarah is an French citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 44, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'LANGUAGE'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
WHO follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 29, 'LAW')]"
Sophia is an Japanese citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 49, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
UNICEF raised €1 billion in August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (28, 37, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
UNICEF announced a new PlayStation on Monday.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Sydney.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 53, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in New York.,"[(41, 49, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Michael donated $100 to Apple.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (24, 29, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'MONEY')]"
Robert is an French citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (13, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
David visited New York during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
David donated $100 to Netflix.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 29, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Alice donated €200 to Netflix.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 29, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
David wrote about Starry Night in English.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 41, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Michael visited Berlin during the Olympics.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (16, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 42, 'EVENT')]"
Olivia is an Japanese citizen working in London.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 47, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Alice wrote about Mona Lisa in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (31, 37, 'LANGUAGE'), (31, 37, 'NATIONALITY')]"
"Olivia donated ₹50,000 to UN.","[(0, 6, 'PER'), (26, 28, 'ORG'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
Olivia donated $100 to Tesla.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 28, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
UN announced a new Pixel 8 on April.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (30, 35, 'DATE'), (19, 26, 'PRODUCT')]"
Alice donated $5 million to Tesla.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 33, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by NASA at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Sophia visited Toronto during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Apple raised $5 million in April.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (27, 32, 'DATE'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Rome.,"[(41, 45, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in Tokyo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Microsoft follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 26, 'LAW')]"
Tesla follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 31, 'LAW')]"
NASA announced a new Surface Pro on Monday.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (36, 42, 'DATE'), (21, 32, 'PRODUCT')]"
Amazon announced a new PlayStation on June 5.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Microsoft announced a new iPhone on January 1st.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (36, 47, 'DATE'), (26, 32, 'PRODUCT')]"
Tesla announced a new Surface Pro on April.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (37, 42, 'DATE'), (22, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Liam is an American citizen working in Cairo.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 44, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Netflix announced a new PlayStation on Monday.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (39, 45, 'DATE'), (24, 35, 'PRODUCT')]"
Alice wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 45, 'LANGUAGE')]"
UNICEF raised €1 billion in August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (28, 37, 'DATE'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
NASA follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (17, 21, 'LAW')]"
Google announced a new iPhone on 2023.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (33, 37, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
PlayStation was launched by Amazon at the World Cup.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
"Olivia donated ₹50,000 to Tesla.","[(0, 6, 'PER'), (26, 31, 'ORG'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
Sarah donated $100 to Tesla.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 27, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Microsoft follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (22, 32, 'LAW')]"
Emma wrote about Mona Lisa in French.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (30, 36, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Tesla raised $100 in January 1st.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 32, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Apple at the Comic-Con.,"[(24, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 46, 'EVENT')]"
Apple announced a new Surface Pro on December 2024.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (37, 50, 'DATE'), (22, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Microsoft announced a new Pixel 8 on August 15.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (37, 46, 'DATE'), (26, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Tesla at the Olympics.,"[(28, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 49, 'EVENT')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
David is an French citizen working in London.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (38, 44, 'LOC'), (12, 18, 'LANGUAGE'), (12, 18, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Alice visited Sydney during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 42, 'EVENT')]"
John donated €1 billion to WHO.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (27, 30, 'ORG'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Liam visited Cairo during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 18, 'LOC'), (30, 39, 'EVENT')]"
Amazon follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 32, 'LAW')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Amazon at the Super Bowl.,"[(27, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 51, 'EVENT')]"
Microsoft announced a new MacBook Pro on June 5.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (41, 47, 'DATE'), (26, 37, 'PRODUCT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Toronto.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 54, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Rome.,"[(38, 42, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Tesla raised €1 billion in April.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (27, 32, 'DATE'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
iPhone was launched by WHO at the World Cup.,"[(23, 26, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Sarah visited Paris during the Olympics.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 39, 'EVENT')]"
WHO announced a new Galaxy S22 on 2023.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (34, 38, 'DATE'), (20, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple raised €200 in January 1st.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 32, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
UN announced a new PlayStation on December 2024.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (34, 47, 'DATE'), (19, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
WHO follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 21, 'LAW')]"
Liam is an Indian citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (37, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 17, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sophia donated €200 to Apple.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 28, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
Surface Pro was launched by NASA at the Olympics.,"[(28, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 48, 'EVENT')]"
David wrote about Guernica in English.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 37, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Emma is an American citizen working in Berlin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Tesla follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Apple at the World Cup.,"[(28, 33, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (41, 50, 'EVENT')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(37, 45, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
NASA announced a new iPhone on December 2024.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (31, 44, 'DATE'), (21, 27, 'PRODUCT')]"
Apple follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 22, 'LAW')]"
iPhone was launched by NASA at the Olympics.,"[(23, 27, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (35, 43, 'EVENT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Microsoft at the World Cup.,"[(27, 36, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (44, 53, 'EVENT')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Amazon at the Olympics.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 46, 'EVENT')]"
David wrote about Starry Night in Hindi.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by Microsoft at the Coachella.,"[(27, 36, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (44, 53, 'EVENT')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(47, 53, 'LOC'), (4, 10, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Tesla follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 28, 'LAW')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in Sydney.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Netflix at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 35, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (43, 52, 'EVENT')]"
WHO follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'LAW')]"
Emma is an Canadian citizen working in Toronto.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 46, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Robert donated €1 billion to WHO.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 32, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
UN follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (15, 28, 'LAW')]"
David wrote about Starry Night in Spanish.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 41, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Netflix raised $5 million in April.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (29, 34, 'DATE'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
David visited New York during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Tesla raised $100 in January 1st.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (21, 32, 'DATE'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
David donated $100 to Amazon.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 28, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Google announced a new Kindle on 2023.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (33, 37, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
Google follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
The Sydney Opera House is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(4, 10, 'LOC'), (47, 52, 'LOC'), (4, 22, 'FACILITY')]"
Sarah visited Paris during the World Cup.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Cairo.,"[(44, 49, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in London.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
Galaxy S22 was launched by WHO at the Comic-Con.,"[(27, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 10, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
UN follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'LAW')]"
Netflix follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 24, 'LAW')]"
Michael is an American citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (42, 47, 'LOC'), (14, 22, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Google announced a new MacBook Pro on August 15.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 47, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Olivia donated €200 to Tesla.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (23, 28, 'ORG'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
UN raised $5 million in April.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (24, 29, 'DATE'), (10, 20, 'MONEY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Paris.,"[(44, 49, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Liam wrote about Starry Night in Mandarin.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 29, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (33, 41, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Olivia visited Sydney during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Tesla announced a new iPhone on 2023.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (32, 36, 'DATE'), (22, 28, 'PRODUCT')]"
iPhone was launched by Apple at the Comic-Con.,"[(23, 28, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (36, 45, 'EVENT')]"
Amazon follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 32, 'LAW')]"
UN raised €200 in 2023.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (18, 22, 'DATE'), (10, 14, 'MONEY')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(38, 44, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
UNICEF announced a new iPhone on December 2024.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (33, 46, 'DATE'), (23, 29, 'PRODUCT')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Amazon at the Comic-Con.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Google at the World Cup.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
John donated $100 to UNICEF.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 27, 'ORG'), (21, 23, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
NASA raised €1 billion in 2023.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (26, 30, 'DATE'), (12, 22, 'MONEY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Olivia wrote about The Last Supper in English.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 45, 'LANGUAGE')]"
The Empire State Building is a famous monument in Berlin.,"[(50, 56, 'LOC'), (4, 25, 'FACILITY')]"
"Sophia donated ₹50,000 to UN.","[(0, 6, 'PER'), (26, 28, 'ORG'), (15, 22, 'MONEY')]"
Sophia wrote about The Last Supper in Mandarin.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 34, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 46, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Tesla follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LAW')]"
Robert visited Paris during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 20, 'LOC'), (32, 42, 'EVENT')]"
John visited Berlin during the Olympics.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (13, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 39, 'EVENT')]"
Robert wrote about Starry Night in English.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 42, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Liam is an French citizen working in Sydney.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (37, 43, 'LOC'), (11, 17, 'LANGUAGE'), (11, 17, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Sophia is an Canadian citizen working in Tokyo.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 46, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
The Eiffel Tower is a famous monument in Cairo.,"[(41, 46, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(44, 52, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Google follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
Robert visited Rome during the Comic-Con.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
The Burj Khalifa is a famous monument in Mumbai.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (4, 16, 'FACILITY')]"
Liam donated €200 to NASA.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (21, 25, 'ORG'), (13, 17, 'MONEY')]"
MacBook Pro was launched by Amazon at the Olympics.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 50, 'EVENT')]"
Guernica is displayed at a museum in London.,"[(37, 43, 'LOC'), (0, 8, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Sophia wrote about Starry Night in Hindi.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (19, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (35, 40, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Alice wrote about Starry Night in Hindi.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 39, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Kindle was launched by Microsoft at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 32, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (40, 50, 'EVENT')]"
UN announced a new iPhone on Monday.,"[(0, 2, 'ORG'), (29, 35, 'DATE'), (19, 25, 'PRODUCT')]"
Mona Lisa is displayed at a museum in New York.,"[(38, 46, 'LOC'), (0, 9, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Michael is an French citizen working in New York.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (40, 48, 'LOC'), (14, 20, 'LANGUAGE'), (14, 20, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by Netflix at the Super Bowl.,"[(24, 31, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (39, 49, 'EVENT')]"
Amazon raised €200 in April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (22, 27, 'DATE'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
Robert visited Berlin during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (33, 43, 'EVENT')]"
Olivia is an Canadian citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (41, 45, 'LOC'), (13, 21, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Alice wrote about The Last Supper in Hindi.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 42, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Amazon announced a new PlayStation on June 5.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (38, 44, 'DATE'), (23, 34, 'PRODUCT')]"
Sophia donated €1 billion to Microsoft.,"[(0, 6, 'PER'), (29, 38, 'ORG'), (15, 25, 'MONEY')]"
The Last Supper is displayed at a museum in Berlin.,"[(44, 50, 'LOC'), (0, 15, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
Starry Night is displayed at a museum in London.,"[(41, 47, 'LOC'), (0, 12, 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
UNICEF follows the HIPAA strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 24, 'LAW')]"
WHO follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (16, 20, 'LAW')]"
iPhone was launched by Google at the Super Bowl.,"[(23, 29, 'ORG'), (0, 6, 'PRODUCT'), (37, 47, 'EVENT')]"
Surface Pro was launched by Amazon at the World Cup.,"[(28, 34, 'ORG'), (0, 11, 'PRODUCT'), (42, 51, 'EVENT')]"
David donated $5 million to Tesla.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (28, 33, 'ORG'), (14, 24, 'MONEY')]"
Apple announced a new PlayStation on January 1st.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (37, 48, 'DATE'), (22, 33, 'PRODUCT')]"
WHO raised $100 in Monday.,"[(0, 3, 'ORG'), (19, 25, 'DATE'), (11, 15, 'MONEY')]"
Michael visited London during the Super Bowl.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (16, 22, 'LOC'), (34, 44, 'EVENT')]"
Netflix follows the Copyright Law strictly.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (20, 33, 'LAW')]"
Alice visited Tokyo during the World Cup.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (14, 19, 'LOC'), (31, 40, 'EVENT')]"
Netflix raised $100 in June 5.,"[(0, 7, 'ORG'), (23, 29, 'DATE'), (15, 19, 'MONEY')]"
NASA follows the Patent Act strictly.,"[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (17, 27, 'LAW')]"
John is an Canadian citizen working in Rome.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (39, 43, 'LOC'), (11, 19, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Tesla raised $5 million in Monday.,"[(0, 5, 'ORG'), (27, 33, 'DATE'), (13, 23, 'MONEY')]"
Alice wrote about Starry Night in French.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (18, 30, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 40, 'LANGUAGE'), (34, 40, 'NATIONALITY')]"
"Alice donated ₹50,000 to Netflix.","[(0, 5, 'PER'), (25, 32, 'ORG'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
John wrote about Mona Lisa in Spanish.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 37, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Microsoft announced a new MacBook Pro on January 1st.,"[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (41, 52, 'DATE'), (26, 37, 'PRODUCT')]"
Alice donated €200 to Microsoft.,"[(0, 5, 'PER'), (22, 31, 'ORG'), (14, 18, 'MONEY')]"
UNICEF follows the GDPR strictly.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (0, 2, 'ORG'), (19, 23, 'LAW')]"
"David donated ₹50,000 to Microsoft.","[(0, 5, 'PER'), (25, 34, 'ORG'), (14, 21, 'MONEY')]"
Liam wrote about Guernica in French.,"[(0, 4, 'PER'), (17, 25, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (29, 35, 'LANGUAGE'), (29, 35, 'NATIONALITY')]"
Amazon announced a new Pixel 8 on April.,"[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (34, 39, 'DATE'), (23, 30, 'PRODUCT')]"
Pixel 8 was launched by UNICEF at the Coachella.,"[(24, 30, 'ORG'), (24, 26, 'ORG'), (0, 7, 'PRODUCT'), (38, 47, 'EVENT')]"
